Guide to the Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0672
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 1997-1998; Accession ARCH-2000-203
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 9/24/97 - 8/27/98; O 3.43 (Box 13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 9/10/97 - 10/13/97; O 3.44 (Box 13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 10/24/1997 - 12/11/97; O 3.44 (Box 13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 12/17/97 - 2/23/98; O 3.44 (Box 13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 3/9/98 - 5/18/98; O 3.44 (Box 13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 5/22/98 - 8/28/98; O 3.44 (Box 13)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 9/2/97 - 11/24/97; O 3.47 (Box 14)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 11/12/97 - 2/13/98; O 3.47 (Box 14)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 2/20/98 - 5/28/98; O 3.47 (Box 14)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 5/29/98 - 8/31/98; O 3.47 (Box 14)
  - CA Business Higher Education Forum, 9/17/97 - 4/3/98; O 3.56 (Box 14)
  - Athletic Awards Miscellaneous, 9/30/97 - 8/6/98; O 4 (Box 14)
  - Political Groups, Miscellaneous, 10/8/97 - 1/16/98 only; O 6 (Box 14)
  - Research Organizations, Miscellaneous, 9/26/97 - 7/29/98; O 7 (Box 14)
  - Institute for Civil Injustice - RAND Corporation, 5/1/98 only; O 7.9 (Box 14)
  - National Research Council (NRC), 3/4/98 - 4/3/98 only; O 7.11 (Box 14)
  - University Research Association, 10/10/97 - 6/16/1998; O 7.16 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 9/2/97 - 11/24/97; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 12/3/97 - 1/29/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 2/9/98 - 4/22/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 5/10/98 - 6/12/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 6/16/98 - 6/30/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 7/1/98 - 7/21/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 7/23/98 - 8/18/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 8/21/98 - 8/28/98; O 8 (Box 14)
  - American Association of Universities - [Note: Presidents Reports, Washington Reports, Washington News Summaries, & Research Reports were all tossed], 9/1/97 - 8/31/98 [Filed Selectively]; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34212; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34242; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34273; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34303; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34334; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34365; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34393; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34424; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34454; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34485; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34515; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - American Association of Universities, 34546; O 8.7 (Box 15)
  - Assoc. of Governing Boards of Universities & Colleges (AGB), 10/20/97 - 4/27/98; O 8.8 (Box 15)
  - Assoc. of Independent California Colleges & Univ. (AICCU), 9/5/97 - 8/28/98; O 8.9 (Box 15)
  - Cal Tech, 9/17/97 - 4/25/98; O 8.16 (Box 15)
  - California State Universities, O 8.17 (Box 15)
  - Columbia University, 9/5/97 - 12/15/97 only; O 8.18 (Box 15)
  - Cornell University, 6/23/98 only; O 8.19 (Box 15)
  - Harvard University, 9/10/97 - 7/17/98; O 8.23 (Box 15)
  - Peking University, 10/9/97 - 8/21/98; O 8.30 (Box 15)
  - Princeton University [This info was originally archived with the '98 pull, but was retreived as a result of needing the '92-'94 accreditation file. Instructions were to archive with the next archive period]., *10/23/95 - 4/1/96; O 8.36 (Box 15)
  - Princeton University, 9/29/97 - 8/19/98; O 8.36 (Box 15)
  - Nine Provosts, 1/19/98 - 5/6/98; O 8.39 (Box 15)
  - Univ. of CA (All Campuses), 9/17/97 - 8/31/98; O 8.43 (Box 15)
  - University of Chicago, 9/18/97 - 6/5/98; O 8.44 (Box 15)
  - University of Michigan, 4/1/98 - 4/6/98 only; O 8.45 (Box 15)
  - Brigham Young University, 7/9/98 only; O 8.46 (Box 15)
  - University of Oregon, 6/10/1998 only; O 8.47 (Box 15)
  - University of Southern California, 9/26/97 - 5/12/98; O 8.49 (Box 15)
  - Western Association of Schools & Colleges (WASC), 9/25/97 - 7/7/98; O 8.52 (Box 15)
  - Yale University, * 5/29/97 Re: Smart Product Design/Dr. Ed Carryer; O 8.53 (Box 15)
  - Inaugurations - other schools, 11/26/97 - 8/31/98; O 8.55 (Box 16)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 9/10/97 - 11/24/97; O 11 (Box 16)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 11/26/97 - 4/9/98; O 11 (Box 16)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 4/10/98 - 7/23/98; O 11 (Box 16)
  - California Council on Science & Technology, 3/4/98 - 6/23/98 only; O 12 (Box 16)
  - German American Academic Council Foundation (GAAC), O 14 (Box 16)
  - American Philosophical Society, 9/9/97 - 8/31/1998; O 15 (Box 16)
  - German Educational Issues, Gov't Studies, 2/5/98 - 8/17/98; O 17 (Box 16)
  - German Educational Issues, Gov't Studies, O 17 (Box 16)
  - German Stuff, Misc., O 19 (Box 16)
  - Research Misc., 9/3/97 - 8/21/98; R 0 (Box 16)
  - Sponsored Projects, 1/30/98 - 7/6/1998; R 1 (Box 16)
  - Stanford Center for Chicano Research (CSSR), 9/16/97 - 3/26/98; R 1.3 (Box 16)
  - Inst. for Research on Women/Gender (same as CROW), 10/15/97 - 7/29/98; R 1.8 (Box 16)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), * 3/9/93 From: Wally Falcon/RE: internationalizing Stanford; R 1.12 (Box 16)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 9/2/97 - 11/26/97; R 1.12 (Box 16)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 12/2/97 - 1/14/98; R 1.12 (Box 16)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 1/26/98 only; R 1.12 (Box 16)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 1/28/98 - 7/30/98; R 1.12 (Box 16)
  - Bio X Project, R 2 (Box 16)
  - Stanford Leadership Institute, R 7 (Box 16)
  - The Science Coalition, 9/5/97 - 7/1/98; R 8 (Box 16)
  - Students (Misc.), 9/8/97 - 8/10/98; ST 1 (Box 16)
  - Student (Groups), 9/22/97 - 8/10/1998; ST 1.1 (Box 16)
  - Ram's Head/Gaeities, 1/12/98 - 4/6/98 only; ST 1.3 (Box 16)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 9/5/97 - 11/19/97; ST 2 (Box 16)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 11/21/97 - 8/5/98; ST 2 (Box 16)
  - Stanford Band, 1/1/98 - 8/31/98; ST 3.4 (Box 16)
  - Bechtel International Center, 10/14/97 - 7/29/98; ST 3.5 (Box 16)
  - Hillel, 12/15/97 - 8/3/98; ST 3.7 (Box 16)
  - KZSU, 11/11/97 - 6/8/98; ST 3.18 (Box 16)
  - Haas Public Service Center (T. Stanton), 9/26/97 - 2/6/98; ST 3.29 (Box 16)
  - Haas Public Service Center (T. Stanton), 3/2/98 - 8/31/98; ST 3.29 (Box 16)
  - Gardner, John - Fellowship, 10/27/97 - 4/15/98; ST 3.29/1 (Box 16)
  - Campus Compact, 9/19/97 - 8/25/98; ST 3.35 (Box 16)
  - ASIA-PACIFIC Scholars Program, 9/2/97 - 8/10/98; ST 7.1 (Box 16)
  - Student/Parent Correspondence, 9/2/97 - 8/17/98; ST 8 (Box 16)
- President's travel and expense records, 1992-1998; Accession ARCH-2000-204
  - Travel, university-related
    - Chicago (Celebration '98), 35945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Washington, D.C. (SIW 10th Anniv./AAU Spring Mtg/Carnegie Corp), 4/16-21/98 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco (Mtg w/Thom Weisel, John Gunn, John Levin, Claude Rosenberg), 35884 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles (Susan Prager, Walter Weisman, Brad Freeman, John Walsh, Kenneth August, Ed Johnson.), 3/18-20/98 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cambridge, MA (Nat'l Innovation Summit), 3/12-13/98 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Houston/Dallas, TX - OOD (Peter Coneway, Jay Anthony Precourt, Stewart Cureton, Jr.) C. Vin Prothro, Jim Adams, James Hoak, David Laney, Tom Rhodes), 2/24-25/98 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Vancouver, British Columbia and Seattle (Alumni Reception; Mtgs with Bill Neukom, Pigott Reception), 2/17-18/98 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Stockholm, Uppsala, Kista (Royal Dinner, Wallenberg mtg, Wallquist Dinner), 12/9-13/97 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Hong Kong, Thailand, India - OOD, 10/29-11/10/97 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - NYC (AAU Fall Meeting), 10/18-23/97 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Denver, San Diego (AAU Mtg / Mtg w/Dick Atkinson, Charles Gates, Philip Anschutz, Malin Burnham, Tim Wollaeger, Ivor Royston), 8/27-29/97 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - NYC, Cambridge, Beverly Shores (Eleanor Alter, Ward Woods, Maurice Hank Greenberg, Tanner Trustees, Allie Kurland and Frieds, 6/17-23/97 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Baltimore, NYC (Symposium-A Leader of Character-Annapolis; Richters; NY Times Editorial Board; Banquet of the Golden Plate), 5/20-23/97 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Santa Barbara and San Diego (CA Bus Higher Ed. Fdn), 4/17-20/97 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - NY and Washington, D.C. (John Eastman, Ronald Lauder, Herald Ritch, Bill Bowen, Ward Woods, Vicky Sant, Carla Hills, Ted Koppel, Sharon Rockefeller, Neal Pings, John Vaughn), 4/1-4/97 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Los Angeles Robert Day, Brad Freeman, Charles Thornton, William Baribault, David Collins, Ron Spogli, 3/12-14/97 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Sacramento (Major Gift Donor/Morton Friedman, Stanford Alumni Reception), 34003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Sun Bowl, El Paso, TX, 12/30-31/96 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Washington, D.C. (Bob Matsui, Cal Dooley, James Fallows, The Future of Research Univ. in the Information Age, AAU Exec. Comm. Conference Call., 12/2-4/96 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Princeton, NJ 250th Anniversary Convocation Procession, Princeton Univ., 33901 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Pasadena, CA (AAU Fall Meeting), 10/20-22/96 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Chicago & Martha's Vineyard Tanner Meeting, 7/26-28/96 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Portland, OR (CEO/Tournament of Roses mtg / Imperial Tombs of China / Major Prospects by Helena Lankton, Selwyn Bingham / Portland Younger Alumni / Eric Hoffman / David Munro / Robert Wulf / William Swindells / Julie Vader / Stanford Alumni Assoc. mtg.), 6/1-4/96 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Japan / Hong Kong / Singapore (Takeo Ohbayashi / Emperor/Empress of Japan / etc.), 5/10-19/96 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Pasadena / Palm Springs (Huntington Library / Bob Skotheim, Marylyn Warren) / Jim Dickason, Bud McDuffie / George & Maggie Jagels / Bill Baribault / Chuck & Geneva Thornton / W Annenberg, 4/24-25/96 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - California Business - Higher Education Forum (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Washington, D.C. AAU Spring Membership Meeting, 4/13-16/96 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Los Angeles / Denver OOD / Bing Dinner/Franklin Visit/Ethnic Reception/Anschutz Visit..., 3/16-18/96 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Salt Lake City, UT Latter Day Saints, 33668 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Orange County, CA Voogd / OC Luncheon / Koll / Argyros / TSF Reception / Town Hall, 33654 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Atlanta, GA Presidents Work Gruop on Accreditation, 1/30-31/96 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - NYC, NY OOD / Ralph & Christiane Fraise / Joel Fleishman & Harvey Dale / Wall St. Jrnl/Bundeskanzler Scholarship, 1/17-19/96 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Dallas (Alumni Assoc. & OOD), 1/8-9/96 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Philadelphia, PA Pew Trusts & ALI Council, 12/5-8/95 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Japan / Korea / Taiwan Obayashi Corp. / Tong Yang Group / Microelectronics, 10/30-11/10/95 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Boulder, CO AAU Membership Meeting, 10/15-17/95 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - NYC - Stanford Conference, 9/15-16/95 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Salt Lake City, Utah (OOD / Stanford Fund Donor reception / Alumni Reception in the Shea's garden), 9/8-9/95 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Stanford Sierra Camp, 5/26-28/1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Chicago, IL American Law Institute (ALI); MacArthur Foundation, 5/16-19/95 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - La Quinta, CA ( California Business - Higher Education Forum (CBHEF) Conference), 4/27-28/95 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Washington, D.C. (AAU Mtg / PAC-10 Conference CEO Mtg.), 4/23-26/95 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Arizona & Southern California (Phoenix Alumni Reception / Mallery Dinner / W. Los Angeles Area Younger Alumni Luncheon ), 3/19-20/95 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Washington, D.C. & Tampa ( Phillips Gallery / AAU Committee), 2/28/95 - 3/4/95 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Seattle & Portland (Elwood Howses / Volunteer Luncheon / Pete Higgins / William Swindells / Selwyn Bingham, Jr. ), 2/22-24/95 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Sacramento (Judge David Levi / Brooks Firestone / Jack O'Connell / Leroy Greene / George Dunn / Federalist Society of Sacramento ), 2/14-15/95 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - New York (OOD - Tim Portwood / Newsweek / Adele Keogh / Susan Taylor Rosepink/ Maynard Parker / Henry Muller / John Freidenrich), 1/11-13/95 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Southern California, 12/13-15/94 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - (Morton & Marjorie Shaevitz / Donald Koll / Carl Franklin / Los Angeles Young Assoc. Luncheon (Christopher Forman, Rom Pfister and John Spiegel) / Donald Crocker / Bill Hobson / Saul and Karin Pick / Nancy Munger / Peter Bing / Palmer and John Jackson) (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Pittsburgh, PA Commission on Higher Education, 11/16-17/94 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Squaw Valley, CA California Business - Higher Education Forum, 10/27-28/94 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Washington D.C. Arnold & Porter / John Deutch / Congressman Norm Dicks, 10/4-6/94 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Wine Country Robert Mondavi Winery / Bill and Lila Jaeger, 33130 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Chicago, IL Susan Bell / Jon Denney / Hugo Sonnenschein, 9/8/-10/94 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Sierra Camp (Pasadena / Palm Springs Huntington Libr (Bob Skotheim, Marylyn Warren) / Jim Dickason, Bud McDuffie / Goerge & Maggie Jagels /Bill Baribault / Chuck & Geneva Thornton / W Annenberg ), 9/1-6/94 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Los Angeles, CA - Big Sur, CA AICCU Mtg / Rancho Grande, 6/16-17/94 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Washington, D.C. State Dinner honoring The Emperor & Empress of Japan Peter Hoagland / Senator Conrad / Senator Jeff Bingaman, 6/13-14/94 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - San Francisco Bank of San Francisco Lunch / Lorry Lokey / Jay Cahill / Jewish Comm. Fed. Talk, 32995 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Washington, D.C./ Chicago / Minneapolis AAU Mtg / White House Brkfst / George Mason U. Law School / George Wash U. Law School / Landreth Lunch / Stephen Neal / Chicago Lunch / Pritzker / New Student Reception, 4/17-22/94 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Princeton & NYC Princeton Univ., 3/28-31/94 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Paris / London Press / Harriman / GSB Dinner / SAA conference / Boyer / Browne, 3/17-22/94 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Los Angeles, Bakersfield, Fresno Foster Mtg / Forman Mtg /Cantor Dinner /, 2/24-25/94 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Davos, Switzerland / World Economic Forum, 1/26-31/94 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Boston / NYC Boston Volunteer / Eastman/McCormack/Alumni Recept./Luce /Johnson/Clark/Hodgson/ Sloan/Ford/Li/NY Parents/Atlantic/Rockefeller/Woods/Brownwood/ Muller/McClelland, 1/9-14/94 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Washington, DC (GAAC), 12/19-20/93 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Princeton and NYC Princeton / Parker / Olin / Weeden / Gimon, 12/5-10/93 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Fort Worth, TX / Bob Bass Mtg., 11/22-23/93 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Tokyo / Kyoto / Taipei / Hong Kong Honorable Morihiro Hosokawa, etc., 10/30-11/10/93 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Indianapolis / Chicago AAU Mtg., 10/17-20/93 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - German American Academic Council, 32688 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Expense records, 1992-1998
    - Germany & Houston (Pour le merite and Komission), 9/23-29/98 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Austria (Tanner), Germany, Spain, 7/1-21/98 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Chicago (OOD), 5/28-31/98 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Washington DC (ALI), 5/9-14/98 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Beijing, Xi'an (Centennial), 4/30/98 - 5/9/98 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Washington, D.C./NYC (OOD - AAU), 4/16-21/98 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - San Antonio, TX (Trip Cancelled), 3/30-31/98 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 3/18-20/98 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Cambridge, MA (National Innvo. Summit), 3/12-13/98 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Houston, TX (OOD), 2/24-25/98 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Vancouver and Seattle (OOD), 2/17-18/98 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - San Francisco - PAC-10 Meeting, 2/14-15/98 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Bonn, Koln, Munich, 1/27-2/1/98 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Stockholm, Uppsala, Kista, 12/9-13/97 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Hong Kong, Thailand, India, 10/29-11/10/97 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - AAU and OOD/NYC, 10/18-23/97 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Denver and San Diego, 8/27-29/97 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - NYC, Boston (Tanner), 6/17-23/97 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Germany, 5/28-6/7/97 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Baltimore and NYC, 5/20-23/97 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Santa Barbara and San Diego, 4/17-20/97 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - NYC/DC Fundraising, etc., 4/1-4/97 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Los Angeles - Fundraising, etc., 3/12-14/97 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - El Paso, TX - SunBowl, 12/30-31/96 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - SU to Millbrae re UCSF Merger, 33957 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Washington DC: The future of Research Universities, 12/2-4/96 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - AAU Pasadena, ALI Phil, Princeton, 10/20-25/96 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Tanner, Heisenberg, Vacation, 33785 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Portland, 6/1-4/96 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Regina Casper's trip to Asia, 5/10-6/3/96 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Asia, 5/10-21/96 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Pasadena and Palm Springs, CA, 4/24-26/96 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Washington, DC, 4/13-17/96 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Los Angeles/Denver, 3/16-18/96 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Salt Lake City, Utah, 33668 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1/30-31/96 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - NYC, 1/17-19/96 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Orange County, CA, 33623 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Dallas, TX, 1/8-9/96 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Asia, 10/30-11/10/95 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - AAU - Denver, CO, 10/15-17/95 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - NYC Stanford Alumni Association, 9/15-16/95 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - University of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT, 9/8-9/95 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Tanner Mtg., 6/27-7/1/95 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Los Angeles JP Morgan Dinner/Mtg with Donors, 33409 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Chicago, 33373 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Palm Springs, 4/27-28/95 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Washington, D.C., 4/23-26/95 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 33315 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Washington, D.C./Tampa, 2/28-3/25/95 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Pacific Northwest, 33290 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Sacramento, 2/14-15/95 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - NY, 33222 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - San Diego/Los Angeles, 33219 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Pittsburgh, PA, 11/16-17/94 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Reno, NV, 10/24-28/94 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Washington, D.C., 10/4-6/94 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Chicago, IL, 9/8-10/94 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Lake Tahoe, NV [Stanford Sierra Camp], 33116 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Washington, D.C., 7/14-15/94 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Chicago, IL, 7/4-6/94 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Monterey, CA, 6/18-19/94 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 33039 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Washington, D.C., 6/13-14/94 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Washington, D.C., 4/17-22/94 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Chicago, IL, 3/10-13/94 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Princeton, NJ, 3/28-31/94 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Paris, France, 3/16-22/94 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Chicago, IL, 3/9-13/94 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Los Angeles / Bakersfield / Fresno, 2/24-25/94 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Geneva, Switzerland, 1/26-31/94 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - NYC, 1/13-14/94 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Boston, MA / NYC, 1/9-14/94 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Princeton, NJ, 32846 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Washington, D.C., 12/18-20/93 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Japan / Taiwan, 10/31-11/7/93 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Seattle, WA, 6/1-4/93 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Dallas, TX, 32655 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - NYC / Houston / Dallas, TX, 5/4/93 - 5/7/93 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Monterey, CA, 4/19-30/93 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Palm Springs / Wash D.C. / NYC/ Newark, NJ, 4/18-23/93 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Los Angeles / Orange County, 3/10-12/93 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Germany / NYC / Frankfurt / Cologne / Bonn / Essen / Hamburg / Berlin, 2/22-3/2/93 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - San Diego, 3/25-26/93 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Washington, DC, 3/15-17/93 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Palm Springs, CA, 2/11-13/93 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Sacramento, CA, 1/26-27/93 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Washington, DC, 12/11-12/92 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 11/10-11/92 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Washington DC / Charlottesville, VA, 10/30-11/3/92 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Seattle, WA, 10/18-20/92 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Chicago, IL ---> Stanford move, 32408 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - NYC, 6/18-19/92 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Dinner in Palo Alto, 32361 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Stanford, CA (part of transition to Presidency), 32351 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - to SFO (part of transition to Presidency), 7/22-23/92 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Stanford / Los Angeles, 6/22-26/92 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - NYC, 6/18-19/92 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Stanford, CA (part of transition to Presidency), 5/11-17/92 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Stanford, CA (part of transition to Presidency), 4/20-22/92 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Limousine Service Expenses (for Gerhard Casper), 11/10/92-5/27/97 (Box 4, Folder 171)
- UCSF Stanford Health Care Merger Documents, Accession ARCH-2000-205 (Box 1-2)
- President's records, 1998-1999; Accession ARCH-2001-164
  - Provost's Office, 12/8/98 - 8/31/99; AA 1 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Search Committee, AA 1.2 (Box 1)
  - Dean of the Chapel - Academic, 9/24/98 - 1/26/1999; AA 1.8 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 10/5/98 - 7/23/99; AA 1.12 (Box 1)
  - Graduate Students/Studies, Issues, 9/5/98 - 8/19/99; AA 1.13 (Box 1)
  - Emeriti, 9/4/98 - 7/19/99; AA 2.2 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, Faculty/Staff, 62/16/99 - 6/23/99; AA 2.3.3 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), 9/14/98-7/29/99; AA 2.7 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), 9/22/97 - 6/15/98 (Box 1)
  - Fellows of the University, AA 2.9 (Box 1)
  - Teaching & Research Assist/Assoc., 7/29/99 (1Doc); AA 2.11 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Studies/Issues, 10/19/98 - 8/31/99; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General, 11/17/98 - 8/10/99; AA 3.4 (Box 1)
  - US News/World Rpt. Rankings/Ratings, 9/1/97 - 8/31/98; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Ideals/Values (West Culture requirement), AA 3.5.1 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies, 12/3/98 - 5/14/99; AA 3.6 (Box 1)
  - Television, Cable, CH51, etc., 11/10/98 - 8/31/99; AA 3.9.1 (Box 1)
  - Summer Programs, et al, 3/31/99 - 6/29/99; AA 3.16 (Box 1)
  - Sophomore Seminars, 9/2/98 - 6/1/99; AA 3.18.2 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 5/25/99 - 8/29/99; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 5/6/99 - 5/24/99 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 5/22/98 - 12/4/99 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 9/4/98 - 12/18/98 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 11/2/98 - 8/18/99; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 12/1/98 - 6/25/99; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1)
  - Art, Dept of, 5/10/99 - 5/21/99; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, 9/14/98 - 3/20/99; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1)
  - Dance, Dept of, 6/29/99 (1 Doc); AA 4.1.16 (Box 1)
  - Computer Science, Dept of, 9/30/98 - 8/1/99; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1)
  - Drama, Dept of, 11/11/98 - 7/9/99; AA. 4.1.18 (Box 1)
  - Economics, Dept of, 9/11/98 - 6/3/99; AA 4.1.20 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 9/14/98 - 7/29/99; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1)
  - English, Dept of, 11/12/98 - 6/18/99; AA 4.1.21 (Box 1)
  - French & Italian, Dept of, 10/22/98 - 5/14/99; AA 4.1.22 (Box 1)
  - German, Dept of, 12/10/98 - 6/21/99; AA 4.1.24 (Box 1)
  - History, Dept of, 9/9/98 - 8/30/99; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (HMS), 9/15/98 - 5/28/99; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1)
  - Music, Dept of, 9/6/98 - 7/13/99; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1)